opinioninn.com 2017-03-20

# Privacy Policy

OpinionInn is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. OpinionInn is a branded site owned and operated by Orchid Online Research Pvt Ltd. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website and services. By using this website and registering to our service you agree that your personal information will be shared with Orchid Online Research Pvt Ltd where a lower level of privacy protection may apply than in your own country. 

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website and services. By using this website and registering to our service you agree that your personal information will be shared with Orchid Online Research Pvt Ltd where a lower level of privacy protection may apply than in your own country. 

As you can see by this example, SimpleModal can be easily configured to behave like an OSX dialog. With a handful options, 2 custom callbacks and some styling, you have a visually appealing dialog that is ready to use!

### What personally identifiable information does OpinionInn collect from me? 

OpinionInn collects information in several ways from different parts of our network of websites.

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, OpinionInn asks for your name, email address, zip code, household information and personal interests. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to OpinionInn and you can access the various protected areas of the site. 

For a more detailed discussion about the collection of data through cookies, please see the section immediately below.

### What are cookies and how does OpinionInn use them? 

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, OpinionInn may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Some areas on OpinionInn where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. This avoids you having to enter your login information many times in one day.   
Currently, cookies are utilized by OpinionInn within the following four primary categories  
1) Business cookies which operate as a quality control and verification mechanism in connection with the survey process;  
(2) Performance cookies so that traffic patterns and users on the OpinionInn website may be measured and optimized;   
(3) User cookies so that user information may be recorded so as to enhance performance and user experience on the website  
4) Targeting cookies which are utilized to measure web viewing for market research purposes.   
If you do not wish to have your activity and browsing behavior tracked by OpinionInn, you may opt out by contacting our customer support team at panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com. You can opt-out from the setting of such cookies by changing your settings within your browser. Furthermore you can set-up your browser so that the browser is asking you each time before a cookie is dropped on your device. Also you can delete all you cookies on your device within you browser. You can find all information about cookies, browser settings and cookie deletion on http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ If you have further question with regards to cookie settings please contact panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com In addition, from time to time, tracking mechanisms such as cookies or web beacons may be used by third party content and advertisings which you may choose to view while being on the OpinionInn site. You should review the privacy policies of the websites serving this content, as they may allow for the gathering of information to serve advertising on multiple third party websites over which OpinionInn has no control. Please consult the privacy policies of such third party websites for more information. Who is collecting information and for what purpose? OpinionInn collects valuable information, which assists in developing new products and services. When you are on OpinionInn site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with OpinionInn or with any other third party with whom you elect to share such information, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than OpinionInn, the use of your data and personal information will be governed by appropriate confidentiality and security agreements between OpinionInn and such third parties. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service or by electing not to participate in any given survey.   
Promotions that run on OpinionInn may be sponsored by companies other than OpinionInn or may be co-sponsored by OpinionInn and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.   
Any Sensitive Information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If OpinionInn intends to disclose such information to a third party or use it for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure or use. Please be aware that OpinionInn advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit them. The information practices of those websites linked to OpinionInn are not covered by this privacy statement. Please consult the privacy policies of such third party websites for more information.   

##### Who is collecting information and for what purpose? 

OpinionInn collects valuable information, which assists in developing new products and services. When you are on OpinionInn site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with OpinionInn or with any other third party with whom you elect to share such information, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than OpinionInn, the use of your data and personal information will be governed by appropriate confidentiality and security agreements between OpinionInn and such third parties. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service or by electing not to participate in any given survey. Promotions that run on OpinionInn may be sponsored by companies other than OpinionInn or may be co-sponsored by OpinionInn and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.   
Any Sensitive Information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If OpinionInn intends to disclose such information to a third party or use it for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure or use.   
Please be aware that OpinionInn advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit them. The information practices of those websites linked to OpinionInn are not covered by this privacy statement. Please consult the privacy policies of such third party websites for more information.   

##### With whom does OpinionInn share my information?

As a general rule, OpinionInn will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or User Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed.   
Business Partners & Sponsors: OpinionInn may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If any personal data about you were ever to be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give OpinionInn permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer.   
Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate: Under confidentiality agreements, OpinionInn may match user information with third party data. Also, OpinionInn discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.   
Other: OpinionInn may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating OpinionInn’s Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) OpinionInn’s rights or property, other OpinionInn users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. OpinionInn may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.   
Finally, if there is a sale of a majority of the shares or assets of the legal entities owning and operating OpinionInn, you agree that your personal information and data may be transferred or assigned to such new owners.   

##### Children under the age of 13 

Because this website and its surveys are not directed to children under the age of 13, we do not provide memberships to persons under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, please let your parent or guardian know about this Policy and get his or her permission before you give us any of your personal information or demographic information, use our website or participate in surveys. Except as may be required by law, Orchid Online Research will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13 without the parent’s express approval and consent. 

##### Minors Generally 

In some jurisdictions, participation in OpinionInn, its surveys, and other offerings are subject to age restrictions and other limitations, up to age 18. Please consult your local requirements but if you have a specific question or query, please contact: panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com. 

##### Information for Parents/Guardians 

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal information without your permission or consent, Orchid Online Research Pvt Ltd will take reasonable steps to remove that information from the its database at your request. To request removal of your child’s information, please send us an e-mail at panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com and be sure to include in your message the same user name, password, and e-mail address that your child submitted

##### What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information? 

From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt-in to receive information from these third parties, OpinionInn will share your name and email address with them.  
Only OpinionInn (or agents working on behalf of OpinionInn and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers   
As indicated above, you also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies.   

##### What is OpinionInn’s policy on allowing me to update or correct my personally identifiable information?

You may edit your OpinionInn Account Information and your public OpinionInn Profile at any time by using your OpinionInn ID and password   
Your OpinionInn account can be deactivated. Please contact panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com for further instructions about deactivating your OpinionInn account.   
Anyone can request access to or rectification of his or her other personal information collected and used by OpinionInn by contacting us at panelsupport@orchidearesearch.com. Note that your request must be sufficiently precise and a proof of identity will be required.   

##### Are there limits to the number of surveys I can complete?

To ensure that high research standards are met for our clients and the general public, Opinioninn places at its sole discretion a maximum number on the number of surveys a respondent can complete over a given time-period (over a week or day). This maximum number is set, at the sole discretion of OpinionInn, and is based on a variety of factors, and which are subject to change   

##### What other requirements or obligations are placed on me? 

The time you spend to participate in surveys and other offerings on of our websites and other platforms (including mobile) provides valuable feedback to our clients which helps result in better products and services in the marketplace. In return for your participation, you earn incentive towards various awards and also have opportunities for other offerings and prizes. You are solely responsible for the use, purchase and maintenance of your own electronic devices (be they handheld devices, laptops, etc.) and all of the corresponding internet connection, landline, wireless carrier, or other charges that you may incur regarding the use of such devices. You also agree that you will not participate in surveys while operating a moving vehicle, or in any other unsafe situation. You release OpinionInn.com, the survey sponsors, their officers, directors, employees or their affiliates from any claim of damages arising from, or relating to, your response(s) to the notifications on your mobile device and/or while taking a mobile survey.   

##### Can I receive surveys on my mobile devices? 

In addition to websites, some OpinionInn surveys and solutions are offered via mobile devices. You will participate in such surveys only to the extent you expressly agree to participate through this platform. You acknowledge and agree that in such circumstances, mobile tracking functions will be enabled which track your mobile device via position locaters such as Global Positioning System (“GPS”) for the purpose of providing you with customized and timely surveys or related services and initiatives which are tailored to query and/or measure your specific preferences and/or opinions and to provide the most meaningful and timely information to OpinionInn clients and partners. After participating in these offerings, you can elect to opt out at any time. 

When you are participating in OpinionInn surveys and solutions via mobile devices and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with OpinionInn or with any other third party with whom you elect to share such information, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If personally identifiable information is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than OpinionInn, the use of such personal information will be governed by appropriate confidentiality and security agreements between OpinionInn and such third parties. Because OpinionInn surveys and solutions via mobile devices are not directed to children under the age of 13, we do not provide memberships to persons under age 13 for that purpose. Any surveys or solutions via mobile devices are further subject to the requirements set forth in the section above, entitled, “Children under the age of 13”, of this Privacy Policy. 

There may be instances when photographs, video or other imagery of individuals or locations is captured via mobile devices in connection with surveys and other solutions (the “Imagery”). OpinionInn will not utilize the rights of publicity of any individual in connection with the Imagery (or otherwise) without obtaining the proper consents. Any use by you of any Imagery should be utilized for your internal purposes only and any required consents from third parties must be properly obtained. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Orchid Online Research Pvt Ltd., its branches, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, employees and agents from any claims arising out of, or relating to, your unauthorized use of the Imagery. 

Please be aware that other websites and apps may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit or use them. The information practices of those websites and apps linked to OpinionInn are not covered by this privacy statement. Please consult the privacy policies of such third party websites or apps for more information. 

##### What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information? 

Your OpinionInn Account Information and OpinionInn Profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information.  
We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. OpinionInn will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your OpinionInn account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Whenever OpinionInn handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, OpinionInn takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, OpinionInn cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Finally, in the event there are material changes to this policy in the future, OpinionInn will make appropriate announcements and disclosures on this website.
